Giwoo Gustavo Lee

github.com/gglee89 linkedin.com/in/leegiwoo https://gglee89.github.io/GL-Portfolio

Summary

5+ years advancing in the IT industry. Shaped products using Data Engineering with BI, Mainframes (batch processing), and Web/Mobile development. Experienced in developing internal web platforms for the entertainment and financial industry and also with B2C customer facing applications. Actively contributed on UI/UX, software specification, and project management in parallel with web development.

Technical Skills

Main programing languages:

JavaScript and Python.

Database: Firebase, MySQL, MongoDB.

Back End Frameworks/Libraries: NodeJS-Express, Python-Flask.

Front End Frameworks/Libraries: ES6/Next, Webpack, SVG, SCSS, Responsive Design, React, Redux, WebSocket.

Testing Frameworks/Libraries:

Jest, Mocha.

Dev Ops: Git, Docker, Kubernetes, CircleCI, AWS, Google Cloud Platform.

Education

University of Mississippi- PhD Computer Science [Machine Learning]

January 2023

Ajou University - MSc Information Systems [Not completed] (Full Scholarship - GPA 3.7/4.0)

December 2017

University of Mississippi - Visiting student at the CS department (Full Scholarship funded by the Brazilian CAPES Program - GPA 3.5/4.0)

May 2012 - May 2013

Faculdade Impacta de Tecnologia - BSc Information Systems

August 2009 - June 2014

Work Experience

Rocky Robots - Web / Mobile App Developer Remote

Seoul, South Korea | Sep 2018-Today

- Developed admin dashboard and iOS-Android app with React Native to interact with conversational AI agent.

Proof Suite - Front End Developer Contractor

Seoul, South Korea | Feb 2018-July 2018 (6 months)

- Developed crypto finance dashboard and crypto currency trade platform with React, Redux, Stockcharts, D3.js, Socket.io

Marshall Goldsmith SCC - Front Developer

Seoul, South Korea | Jan 2017-Mar 2018 (1 year 1 month)

- Developed executive coaching platform suite with PHP, React, Javascript, Webpack, SASS.

SAP Labs Korea - Web Developer

Seoul, South Korea | *Aug 2015-Feb 2016 (6 months)*

 Developed internal QA platform HDBCSI (Hana DB Crash Similarity Inspector) using Python-Flask, SAP OpenUI5 framework with XSJS (Server-side JS).

FNC Inc. - Software Developer I

Oxford, MS, & Sao Paulo, Brazil | Jun 2013-May 2014 (1 year)

Developed real estate appraisal web application in C#/.Net, TFS (Team Foundation Server), SQL Server, and KnockoutJS.

Amdocs - System Analyst Intern

Sao Paulo, SP, Brazil | *Apr 2011-May 2012 (1 yr)*

- Developed in COBOL as the on-going support for Claro Brasil Telecom - Billing System

Technolab Corp. - BI Consultant Intern

Sao Paulo, SP, Brazil | Sep 2010-Mar 2011 (7 months)

- Assist the implementation of Oracle's BI solutions. Oracle ODI 11g (DW, ETL, DB) and Oracle Golden Gate.

Certification

Facebook Pytorch Scholar - Udacity (Intro to Deep Learning with PyTorch)	January 2019
Machine Learning by Andrew Ng - Coursera	December 2018
Developing Application with Google Cloud Platform Specialization - Coursera	September 2018
Udacity - React Nanodegree	March 2018
Udacity - Front End Nanodegree	December 2017
Udacity - Full Stack Nanodegree	July 2017

Language

Portuguese (Brazil)	Fluent
English	Fluent
Korean	Fluent
Spanish	Intermediate